Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal closed hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold, hands down
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with Left HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left HL for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Embrace for the lady in a shadow), ends with Copa with Embrace hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower from Embrace for the follower standing side by side with the man in a normal hold
Walking around the partner
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with hand drop for the follower
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, right hand throw for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's both hand (hands down, crossed hold)
Right turn for the leader with crossed hold, ending with comb on the follower with leader's right hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, both hands hold, facing the same direction with the leader in front with late half right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, right hand drop for the follower behind the leader facing the same direction
Copa accent on beat 1 with double left turn for the follower facing different directions on the line of dance
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with left hand throw for the follower, normal open hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, late right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) ends with break
Natural top
XBL with normal open hold ends with break
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader with crossed hold
Copa with the follower's right (outside) turn with crossed hold ends with right hand throw
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, crossed hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
[Follower] Lady styling
Lasso on the follower with the leader's right hand and a left turn for the follower
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hand (open hands down, Embrace for the follower in a shadow) with left half-turn for the leader
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold, hands down
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
Copa with the follower's right (outside) turn with crossed hold ends with right hand throw
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with hand drop for the follower and late left turn for the follower
[Leader] Steps sideways on the heels on the beat 2, 4, 6, 8
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Leader] Side step on 1 and point and heel on 6 and 7
[Follower] Steps sideways on the heels on the beat 2, 4, 6, 8
[Leader] Indescribable
[Follower] Steps sideways on the beat 3 and 7
[Leader] Suzy walks
[Follower] Regular Suzy Q
[Leader] Steps forward on 1, 2, 3, kick on 5 and step aside
[Follower] Steps sideways on the heels on the beat 1, 3, 5, 7
[Leader] Mambo taps on beats 5 and 7
[Follower] Right turn with lady styling
[Leader] Point on 1 and step aside on 3
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Leader] Walks forward
[Follower] Swings with accent on 3 and 7
XBL with normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with left hand throw for the follower, normal open hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left HL for the follower
Left turn for the leader with change of directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, both hands hold, facing the same direction with the leader in front with late half right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold facing the same direction
Check by holding the follower's both hand (open hands down, crossed hold)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, comb for the leader
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with crossed hold