Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Regular Suzy Q
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal closed hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Titanic for the lady in a shadow) after XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower.
Coming back from Check for the follower with crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Left turn for the leader with crossed hold
Side basic step with normal open hold, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Back basic step with normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Right turn for the leader with crossed hold, ending with change of directions for the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Double hand throw with crossed hold
[Follower] Lady styling
Single hand throw with crossed hold
Regular Suzy Q
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with crossed hold
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Left turn for the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
XBL with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance