Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, both hands, crossed hold ends with right hand throw
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, late right turn for the leader
Right turn for the leader with crossed hold, ending with comb on the follower with leader's right hand
XBL with a left (inside) with crossed hold while hands change, Check by holding the follower's shoulder
[Follower] Lady styling
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower while hands change starts with right hand throw for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, crossed hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with hands change
Butterfly Copa wth left (inside) turn for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position)
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) with crossed hold while hands change, Check by holding the follower's hand
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, normal onen hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with hands change, ends with right hand throw for the follower, normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, both hands, crossed hold, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold sliding from the follower's left hand to right hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, crossed hold with both hands, ends with Left Half-HL for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower after the Left Half-HL for the follower
XBL with normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with right hand drop for the follower and right hand throw for the follower
Left turn for the follower
Double right turn for the follower with normal open hold
Left hand throw for the follower to Left HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left HL for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower behind the leader to left HL for the leader ends with right elbow lock for the follower
Right hand throw from elbow lock for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
Comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold, ends with Check on the follower's shoulder
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the leader with his left hand
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Double right turn for the follower with normal open hold into left HL for the follower
Butterfly right turn for the follower and left turn for the follower Facing perpendicular to the line of dance ends with comb on the follower with leader's right hand
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) with crossed hold, Check by holding the follower's both hand (open hands down, Embrace for the follower in a shadow)
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the leader with his left hand
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower ends with left hands throw to Embrace for the follower facing the line of dance with crossed hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Embrace for the follower facing the line of dance with crossed hold
Right turn for the leader with normal open hold, ending with comb on the follower with leader's right hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with hands change, ends with right hand throw for the follower, normal open hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, late right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower with arm lock with the leader's right hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold on the right side of the leader, both hands, ends with late right turn for the leader
Lasso on the follower with the leader's right hand ends with check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Embrace for the follower in the shadow)
Standard copa
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, change of directions from facing one side perpendicular to the line of dance to another for the leader: to the left side of the of the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with comb for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) with normal open hold, Check by holding the follower's hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check on the follower's shoulder by the leader's right hand
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the leader with his left hand
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold