XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Embrace for the lady in a shadow), ends with Copa with Embrace hold
[Leader] Man styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with Left HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left HL for the follower, ends with late right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold sliding from the follower's left hand to right hand
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower on the right side of the leader, ends with Left HL for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold, ends with left hand throw with the leader's right elbow
[Leader] Man styling
XBL with a left (inside) with crossed hold, Check by holding the follower's both hand (open hands down, Embrace for the follower in a shadow)
Double right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the leader with his left hand
XBL with normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with hands change into Left Half-HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left Half-HL for the follower, ends with comb on the leader with his left hand
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower while hands change, ends with break
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with  double left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold on the right side of the leader, ends with late half right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower while changing left hand to right hand for the leader, ends with Check on the follower's shoulder by the leader's right hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Embrace for the lady in a shadow), ends with Copa with Embrace hold
[Leader] Man styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with Left HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold on the right side of the leader, both hands, ends with late right turn for the leader
Double right turn for the follower with normal open hold
Copa on 2 with Titanic hold for the follower, left half-turn for the follower with crossed hold, ends with check on the follower's left hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
Right half-turn for the leader, change of directions (Swap Positions) for the follower
Markers Swap issue
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal open hold ends with break
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower while changing right hand to left hand for the leader, ends with Check on the follower's shoulder by the leader's right hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, normal onen hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Embrace for the lady in a shadow), ends with Copa with Embrace hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with Left HL for the follower
Walking around the partner
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader
XBL with a left (inside) with normal open hold with hands change after comb on the follower and left hand throw for the follower
[Leader] Sliding on beat 1, bringing left heel to the right knee, on 3 back step on the left foot on 6
[Follower] Steps on beats 1, 3, 5, 7 on the same spot
[Follower] Steps on beats 1, 3 on the same spot, ends with steps on beats 5, 6, 7
[Leader] Indescribable
[Follower] in-out Suzy Q
[Leader] Mambo taps on 1, 2 and right turn on right foot on 5, 6, 7
[Leader] Indescribable
[Follower] Side basic step with hands variation
[Leader] Side step on 1
[Leader] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal closed hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with left hand throw for the follower, ends with Left HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left HL for the follower
Right turn for the leader, normal open hold, Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
Indescribable