[Leader] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Basic step while getting back to normal closed hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with left hand throw for the follower, ends with Left HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower after the Left Half-HL for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Embrace for the lady in a shadow), ends with Copa with Embrace hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with Left HL for the follower
Walking around the partner
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with hand drop for the follower and late left half-turn for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold, both hands ends with right Sombrero hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction with the follower in front, ends with comb on the leader
Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold ends with break
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower while changing left hand to right hand for the leader, ends with Check on the follower's shoulder by the leader's left hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, both hands hold, change of directions from facing one side perpendicular to the line of dance to another for the leader: to the left side of the of the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower while hands change starts with right hand throw for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower, ends with left hand throw with the leader's right hand into Left HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left HL for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Embrace for the lady in a shadow), ends with Copa with Embrace hold with right hand throw for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower from twist hold, normal open hold, both hands
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Natural top with left half turn for the follower
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check on the follower's shoulder by the leader's right hand
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the leader with his left hand
XBL with normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with hand drop for the follower
[Leader] Sliding on beat 1, bringing left heel to the right knee, on 3 back step on the left foot on 6
[Follower] Steps sideways on the heels on the beat 2, 4, 6, 8
[Leader] Back Points on 1, 2, 3
[Follower] Regular Suzy Q
[Leader] Half Suzie back step, ends with sliding on beat 5, bringing left heel to the right knee on 6
[Follower] in-out Suzy Q
[Leader] Sliding on 1, 2, 3, point on 5, heel on 6
[Leader] Half Suzy Q on beat 1, 2, 3, left knee on 6
[Follower] Left turn while doing steps sideways on the beats 2, 4, 6, 8
[Leader] Change of Directions (Swap Position) from facing along the line of dance to perpendicular to the line of dance
[Follower] Right turn with lady styling
XBL with normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, Check on the follower's shoulder by the leader's right hand, ends with copa with left Half-HL for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) back to crossed hold from Left Half-HL for the follower and left turn for the leader on  beats 5, 6, 7
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, late right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold facing the same direction
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, both hands hold, ends with late half right turn for the leader
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down, crossed hold)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Titanic for the lady in a shadow) after XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower.
[Follower] Lady styling
Change of directions with side-to-side Titanic hold ends with right elbow hand throw for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Titanic for the lady in a shadow) after XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower.
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from side-to-side Titanic hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower