Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check on the follower's shoulder by the leader's right hand
Right turn for the follower, left turn for the leader, crossed hold
Left turn for the follower
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, normal onen hold
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold ends with open break
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
Walking around the leader for the follower by  doing Lasso on the follower with the leader's right hand and check on the follower's shoulder
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction with the leader in front
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower while changing left hand to right hand for the leader, ends with Check on the follower's shoulder by the leader's left hand
[Follower] Lady styling
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, both hands hold, change of directions from facing one side perpendicular to the line of dance to another for the leader: to the left side of the of the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold ends with open break
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with comb for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Titanic for the lady in a shadow) after XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower.
Standard copa
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
XBL with normal closed hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with hand drop for the follower and late right half-turn for the leader
Left turn for the follower with single hand throw
[Follower] Lady styling
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold, left hand throw for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, change of directions from facing one side perpendicular to the line of dance to another for the leader: to the left side of the of the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with hands change
Copa with the follower's right (outside) turn with crossed hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with crossed hold, Comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
Walking around the leader for the follower by  doing Lasso on the follower with the leader's right hand and check on the follower's shoulder
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with hands change, ends with right hand throw for the follower, normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, late right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
[Follower] Lady styling
Change of directions with side-to-side copa wth Titanic hold ends with right elbow hand throw for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold, both hands ends with right Sombrero hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with comb for the leader
XBL with normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with comb for the follower
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) with crossed hold while hands change, Check by holding the follower's both hand (open hands down, Embrace for the follower in a shadow)
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, normal onen hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower starts with right hand throw for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with no hands, ends with natural top
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
XBL with a left (inside) with crossed hold while hands change, Check by holding the follower's hand
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, crossed hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check on the follower's shoulder by the leader's right hand
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold ends with left hand throw to Left HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left HL for the follower, ends with late right turn for the follower
Double right turn for the follower, left turn for the leader with crossed hold ends with right hand drop over the shoulder for the follower
XBL with  double left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold, ends with late half right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, crossed hold
Walking around the leader for the follower by  doing Lasso on the follower with the leader's right hand while hands change and check on the follower's shoulder
[Follower] Man styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower ends with Right HL for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower starts with left hands throw to Embrace for the follower facing the line of dance with crossed hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with hands change
Comb on the follower with the leader's right hand with crossed hold
Lasso on the follower with the leader's left hand
[Follower] Lady styling