Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold
[Leader] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Right turn
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal closed hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal closed hold, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down
Basic step, facing the line of dance with normal closed hand
Right turn for the follower, normal closed hold
Right turn for the leader, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader, change of directions
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, crossed hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Double hand throw with crossed hold
Double hand throw with normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Left turn for the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position)
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Left turn for the leader