Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
[Leader] Side basic step with hips shrug
[Follower] Steps sideways to the left with the left foot on the beat 5
[Follower] Steps sideways on the beat 1 and 5
[Leader] Right turn-around variation
[Follower] Left turn-around on beats 5, 6, 7
[Leader] Back basic step
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
Basic step with styling, facing the line of dance
Basic step while getting back to normal open hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Regular Suzy Q
Half Suzy Q on beat 1, 2, 3
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Double hand throw with crossed hold
Comb on the leader with his left hand with crossed hold, XBL with normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Back basic step with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Left turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Left turn for the leader with crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Basic step, facing the line of dance with Check on the follower's hands with crossed hold
Single hand throw with crossed hold
XBL with crossed hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Basic step, facing the line of dance with Check on the follower's shoulder
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance with Check on the follower's shoulder
Basic step, facing the line of dance