Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal open hold ends with break
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower ends with Right HL for the follower, ends with half right turn for the leader
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, late right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
[Leader] Lady styling
[Follower] Right turn for the leader with normal open hold, ending with comb on the follower with leader's right hand
Change of Directions (Swap Position) ends with break
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
[Leader] Man styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down, crossed hold)
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold sliding from the follower's left hand to right hand
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower on the right side of the leader, ends with Left HL for the follower
XBL with  double left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold on the right side of the leader, ends with late half right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with crossed hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold, both hands ends with right Sombrero hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction with the follower in front, ends with comb on the leader
XBL with normal closed hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Titanic for the lady in a shadow) after XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower.
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with crossed hold, Comb on the leader with the leader's left hand
XBL with normal open hold ends with break
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, both hands hold, ends with late half right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) with normal open hold while hands change, Check by holding the follower's hand
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, crossed hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, both hands hold, ends with late half right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down, crossed hold)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, normal onen hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower while hands change, ends with comb on the leader
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with left hand throw for the follower, ends with Left HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left HL for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) ends with break
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with hands change behind the follower
Copa on 1 with Titanic hold for the follower with change of directions (Swap position) for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower starts with right hand throw for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, crossed hold
[Leader] Man styling
Change of Directions (Swap Position) ends with break
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with hand drop for the follower and late left half-turn for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with left hand throw for the follower, normal open hold
[Leader] Man styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left HL for the follower, ends with late right turn for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold ends with open break
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with hand drop for the follower, double left turn for the follower
[Leader] Drawing circle with the left foot on 1, 2, 3, kick on 5 with the right foot
[Follower] Right turn
[Leader] Steps sideways on the heels on the beat 2, 4, 6, 8
[Follower] Steps sideways on the heels on the beat 2, 4, 6, 8