Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal closed hold, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down
Natural top
[Follower] Lady styling
[Leader] Man styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with a hand throw
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal closed hand, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Side basic step with normal open holds, facing the line of dance
The follower executes a single right turn
[Follower] Lady styling
[Leader] Man styling
Comb on the follower's with the leader's left hand with a normal hold
[Follower] Lady styling
Follower  walks around the leader.
XBL with a left turn for the leader
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction with the leader in front
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Check by holding the follower's hands (closed hands down) after XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower.
Check by holding the follower's hand (open hands down) after XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower.
[Follower] Lady styling
Copa with the follower's double left (inside) turn
[Leader] Man styling
[Leader] Steps with the left foot forward on beat 1
[Follower] Left turn on left foot
[Leader] Basic step while getting back to normal closed hold
[Follower] Basic step while getting back to normal closed hold
[Leader] Man styling
XBL with a right turn variation for the leader
[Follower] Lady styling
Follower's right hand throw by leader's left hand, check by holding the follower's hand (open hands down) and the follower's inside turn
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with check on the follower's hip
[Follower] Lady styling
[Leader] Left turn
[Follower] Copa with the follower's left (inside) turn
360 XBL
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal closed hand, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
[Leader] Man styling
Change of Directions (Swap Position)
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left turn for the leader
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Crossed holds, hand drop with leader's right hand and follower's left hand, XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
[Leader] Man styling
One right turn for the leader, arm loop following a right turn for the follower
[Leader] Lady styling
Reverse right Half-HL for the follower, XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
Facing the same direction, side to side walk change of directions, crossed hands
Standard copa with change of directions, crossed hands
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Body roll for the follower, XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with normal closed hand, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down
Right turn for the follower, left turn for the leader, normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
Comb on the leader with his left hand, Comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
Basic step variation with normal open hold
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Basic step variation, the leader changes direction
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with left (inside) turn for the follower with a normal opend hold, left turn for the leader
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
[Leader] Change of Directions (Swap Position)
[Follower] XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
[Leader] Side basic step with hips shrug
[Follower] Advanced footwork variation
XBL with normal closed hold, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down
[Follower] Lady styling
[Leader] Man styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with a hand throw
[Follower] Lady styling
[Leader] Man styling
Arm lock with the right hand
[Follower] Lady styling
[Leader] Steps sideways to the left with the left foot on the beat 5
[Follower] Steps sideways on the heels on the beat 5 and 7
[Leader] Steps sideways on the heels on the beat 2, 4, 6, 8
[Follower] Side step on 1 and suzy back step on 5 and 7 with shoulder shrug
[Leader] Double right turn on left foot on 1, 2, 3 and single left turn on left foot on 5, 6
[Follower] Copa accent on beat 1 with left turn on left foot
[Leader] Basic step with styling, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Skipping feet on beat 1, 2, 3, body roll on 4, and shoulder shrug on 6, 7
XBL with normal closed hold, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down
[Leader] Man styling
Double right turn for the follower, left turn for the leader with crossed hold
[Follower] Lady styling
Copa with the gollower's right (outside) turn with crossed hold
Double Hand throw with crossed hold and comb on the lady with the leader's right hand
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Crossed hold check with normal open hold
The leader's right turn with crossed hold, the leader ducks under the follower's left hand, ends facing the same direction with the lady in the back and hand drop
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Double hand throw with normal open hold
[Leader] Man styling
Copa with normal open hold on the left side of the leader
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
Follower  walks around the leader with crossed hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, crossed hold, the leader facing perpendicular to the line of dance
[Leader] Man styling
Right turn for the leader with crossed hold, ending with arm lock with the right hand for the leader and change of directions
Comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold
[Leader] Man styling
XBL with normal closed hold, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down