[Leader] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Hip movement and shoulder movement on the same spot
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
Basic step, facing the line of dance with normal closed hand
XBL with normal closed hold, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal closed hold
XBL with normal open hold ends with break
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader
Right turn for the follower with a kick delay, normal open hold
Copa with normal open hold on the left side of the leader and comb on the follower
Copa on 2 with Embrace hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower starts with right hand throw for the follower, ends with late right half-turn for the leader
[Leader] Men styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Copa on 2 with crossed hold on the left side of the leader with the left turn for the follower, ends with left turn for the leader with hand drop
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with no hands after left hand throw
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal closed hold ends with break
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with hand drop for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
Copa on 2 with Titanic hold for the follower with crossed hold, ends with left turn for the leader
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Swing step
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower on the right side of the leader starts with right hand throw for the follower
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal closed hold ends with break
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold, ends with Left HL for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
Change of direction, fake hands swap, ending with comb on the follower with the leader's righ hand and the follower's left hand
Copa with the follower's left (inside) turn by holding the follower's hip
XBL with normal closed hold ends with break
[Follower] Lady styling
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
[Follower] Lady styling
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with Reverse back-to-back Titanic hold from left hand for the follower to right hand for the follower
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with  double left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold on the right side of the leader
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Walks forward with the partner in a Sombrero hold ends with Change of Directions (Swap Position)
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Walks forward with the partner in a Sombrero hold
XBL with a double right (outside) turn for the follower with crossed hold while hands change, ends with double hand throw for the follower
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Comb on the follower with the leader's right hand with left HL for the leader
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold ends with break
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the leader
XBL with a left (inside) with normal open hold with hands change after comb on the follower and left hand throw for the follower
Basic step with styling, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
Enchufla with normal open hold with left turn for the leader
[Follower] Lady styling
Enchufla with crossed hold, left turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold facing the same direction ends with Sombrero hold
Arm lock with the leader's right hand with crossed hold, both hands, ends with right hand throw for the follower
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Walking around the partner
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
[Leader] Steps on the same spot on the beats 1 and 3 ends with quick right turn
[Follower] Steps on the same spot on the beats 1 and 3 ends with body roll
[Leader] Steps on the same spot on the beats 1, 3 and with delay on 5
[Follower] Left turn while doing steps sideways on the beats 2, 4, 6, 8
[Leader] Basic step with styling, facing the line of dance with delay on the beat 2
[Follower] Suzy Q
[Leader] Cross basic steps on beats 5 and 7
[Follower] Right turn
[Leader] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Leader] Body roll
[Follower] Quick left turn
XBL with normal open hold
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Triple right turn for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold, right turn for the leader
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
[Leader] Doubel right turn
[Follower] Quick left turn
[Leader] Standing on the same spot on the beats 1, 2 and 3
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Leader] Point on 1 and step aside on 3
[Follower] Quick left turn
XBL with normal open hold ends with break
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold, with hand drop ends with Left HL for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader with left turn for the leader, ends with comb for the leader
Double hand throw with normal open hold into double HL
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with Reverse back-to-back Titanic hold from left HL for the follower, ends with late half-turn for the leader while hands change
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Titanic for the lady in a shadow) after XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower.
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling