Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader with crossed hold, ending with change of directions for the follower
Left turn for the leader
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, Right Half-HL for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) back to normal open hold from Right HL for the lady
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
XBL with normal open hold, starts with Comb on the leader with his right hand
Basic step, facing the line of dance with normal closed hand
XBL with normal closed hold
Basic step while getting back to normal closed hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
XBL with normal open hold, starts with Comb on the leader with his right hand
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Basic step variation with crossed hold
Double hand throw with crossed hold
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, right hand throw for the follower
XBL with crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal closed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance with normal closed hand
XBL with normal closed hold
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the leader with his right hand
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Side basic step with hips shrug
[Leader] Side basic step with hips shrug
[Follower] Side basic step with hands variation
[Follower] Back basic step
[Leader] Right turn
[Follower] Right turn
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Left turn for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Left turn for the leader
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
[Leader] Side basic step with hips shrug
[Follower] Side basic step with hips shrug
[Follower] Side basic step with hands variation
[Leader] Right turn
[Follower] Right turn
Basic step, facing the line of dance