Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader with crossed hold, ending with change of directions for the follower
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Leader] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Leader] Regular Suzy Q
[Follower] Regular Suzy Q
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader with crossed hold, ending with change of directions for the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Left turn for the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Single hand throw with crossed hold
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Double hand throw with crossed hold
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold
Left turn for the leader
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
[Leader] Man styling
Back basic step with normal open hold
Basic step while getting back to normal closed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Leader] Steps sideways on the beat 1 and 5
[Follower] Basic step in place
[Leader] Side step on 1 and double cross back step on 5 and 7
[Follower] Steps sideways to the left with the left foot on the beat 5
[Leader] Basic step in place and side step
[Follower] Basic step on 1 and heel-toe-heel on 5, 6, 7
[Leader] Side basic step with hips shrug
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Leader] Turning around while stepping on each beat
[Follower] Right turn
Basic step while getting back to normal closed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance with normal closed hand
XBL with normal closed hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold