Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position)
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold
XBL with normal closed hold, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change on the back of the leader and then over the follower
Right hand throw for the follower, crossed hold
[Follower] Lady styling
Double hand throw with normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Left hand throw for the follower, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
Side basic step with normal open hold, facing the line of dance
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader, change of directions
Right hand throw for the follower, crossed hold
[Follower] Lady styling
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with Left HL for the lady
Change of Directions (Swap Position) back to normal open hold from Left HL for the lady
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Left turn for the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position)
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with crossed hold
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Cross back basic step with nomal open hold
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
[Leader] Back basic step
[Follower] Back basic step