Indescribable
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with Left HL for the follower
Walking around the partner
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal closed hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with normal open hold
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold, ends with Left HL for the follower
Walking around the partner
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold ends with open break
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower on the right side of the leader, ends with Left HL for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) back to crossed hold from Left HL for the lady ends with elbow hand throw for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
Left turn for the follower, right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, right hand throw for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, late right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold, sliding from the follower's right hand to the same right hand
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower on the right side of the leader, ends with Left HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold on the right side of the leader, both hands, ends with late right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, Left Half-HL for the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold, right turn for the leader
Left turn for the follower, right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold facing the same direction, ends with comb on the follower
XBL with normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with right hand drop for the follower and right hand throw for the follower, late half-turn for the leader
Left turn for the follower, ends with comb on the leader
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold ends with break
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with crossed hold
XBL with  double left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold, ends with late half right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower while hands change from normal open hold to crossed hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) with crossed hold, Check by holding the follower's both hands, ends with left comb on the follower
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, ends with comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower while hands change, ends with comb on the follower
XBL with normal open hold ends with break
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, comb for the leader
XBL with normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, both hands, crossed hold, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with late half right turn for the leader
[Follower] Lady styling
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with normal open hold, Comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
Natural top followed by XBL with left (inside) turn for the follower by holding the follower's shoulder
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold ends with break
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) with normal open hold, Check by holding the follower's hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, late right turn for the leader
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with normal open hold, Comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower with hands change
Copa with the follower's right (outside) turn with crossed hold ends with right hand throw
XBL with  double left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold, ends with late half right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, crossed hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower while hands change