Open break, normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hand (open hands down, Embrace for the follower in a shadow)
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, crossed hold, facing the same direction with the leader in front
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with crossed hold, Comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction with the follower in front, ends with Check by holding the follower's both hands (hands down, open position)
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold
XBL with normal closed hold to normal open hold, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check on the follower's shoulder by the leader's right hand
[Follower] Lady styling
The leader change direction perpendicular to the dance line, XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, normal open hold
Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down), right turn for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, both hands hold, facing the same direction with the leader in front after late half right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold, right hand throw for the follower, half right turn for the leader
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, crossed hold, the leader facing perpendicular to the line of dance
Left turn for the leader perpendicular to the dance line, right turn for the follower while the leader is in front, crossed hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with left hand throw for the follower, normal open hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower from Left HL for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hand (open hands down, Embrace for the follower in a shadow)
Right turn for the follower, comb on the follower with the leader's right hand, normal onen hold
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Titanic for the lady in a shadow) after XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower.
[Follower] Lady styling
Walk back facing the same direction, side to side, ends with copa in Titanic hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with normal open hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, facing the same direction on the right side of the leader, ends with comb for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, comb for the leader
XBL with normal closed hold, the leader's right to the follower left, hands down
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with Left Half-HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower after the Left Half-HL for the follower, ends with a left hand throw for the follower behind the follower
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
[Leader] Change of Directions from Facing the opposite direction (back to back) to Facing perpendicular to the line of dance
[Follower] Right turn
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, late right turn for the leader
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, both hands hold, change of directions from facing one side perpendicular to the line of dance to another for the leader: to the left side of the of the follower
Change of Directions (Swap Position)
[Follower] Lady styling
[Leader] Back basic step with left foot heel on the beat 6, bringing left heel to the right knee on 7
[Follower] Right turn
[Leader] Steps sideways on the beat 1 and 5
[Follower] Steps sideways on the beat 1 and 5
[Leader] Points on beats 2 and 4, ends with half Jazz point Suzie
[Follower] Regular Suzy Q
[Leader] Twisting on beat 1, 2, 3 with right foot, left heel on the beat 6, bringinf left heel to the right knee on 7
[Follower] Points on even beats
[Leader] Advanced footwork variation
[Follower] Right turn
Basic step while getting back to normal closed hold
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with Left Half-HL for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower after the Left Half-HL for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Embrace for the lady in a shadow)
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower, ends with Check by holding the follower's hand (hands down)
Lasso on the follower with the leader's right hand and a left turn for the follower
[Leader] Man styling
[Follower] Lady styling
Early right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, ends with comb on the follower with the leader's right hand
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with normal open hold, hands down
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
Check by holding the follower's both hands (open hands down, Embrace for the lady in a shadow), ends with Copa with Embrace hold
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower, ends with Left HL for the follower
The follower walks around the leader, both hands hold, the leader's right hand leads in a normal open hold