Basic step variation with crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a right (outside) turn for the follower
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower with crossed hold, hands down
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Change of Directions (Swap Position) with crossed hold
Right turn for the leader, crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Regular Suzy Q
[Leader] Indescribable
[Follower] Indescribable
[Leader] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
[Follower] Right turn
[Leader] Right turn
[Follower] Basic step, facing the line of dance
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader with crossed hold, ending with change of directions for the follower
Right hand throw for the follower, crossed hold
Double hand throw with crossed hold
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold
Left turn for the leader
Basic step, facing the line of dance
XBL with a left (inside) turn for the follower
Check by holding the follower's shoulder (hands down), normal open hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Right turn for the follower, normal open hold
XBL with normal open hold
Right turn for the leader, right turn for the follower, normal open hold, hands change behind the leader and then over the follower
Left turn for the leader with crossed hold
Right turn for the follower, crossed hold
Change of Directions (Swap Position) for the follower with crossed hold
Basic step, facing the line of dance
Back basic step with normal open hold
Side basic step with normal open hold, facing the line of dance